iospress.com 2019-12-12

# IOS Press

### Privacy Policy

[https://www.iospress.com](https://www.iospress.com/) is the Corporate Website of IOS Press, registered at Nieuwe Hemweg 6B, 1013 BG, The Netherlands.

Guarding your privacy is very important to us. In this Privacy Policy you can learn which data IOS Press collects via this site and how it is used. It is our goal to provide you with a useful, hassle-free experience while using this website, which requires a certain amount of data collection. If you do not agree with the policies set forth in this Privacy Policy, we recommend that you do not visit the IOS Press Corporate website.

If you are simply browsing our site without leaving your contact details in a form or our payment module for ordering, we will only keep anonymized log data about usage of our site (see ‘Cookies’ below).

**Which details are collected?**

  * Contact details that you have provided to us, including demographics
  * Information on usage of (parts) of our website
  * Information about transactions made
  * Any other information that you have provided to us in order to be able to help you use our website to meet your needs as well as possible

**How IOS Press uses the data collected  
**We may use the data collected through our site to:

  * Establish and verify the identity of our users
  * Personalize the site for you
  * Enable you to access and use our site
  * Fine-tune our services provided to you
  * Handle financial transactions smoothly and accurately
  * Collect payments from you
  * Improve our products and services offered on the IOS Press Corporate Website

**Service Providers and Third Parties  
**We may employ service providers and individuals to facilitate (parts of) our services. In the event that we share the data gathered with service providers working on our behalf, they must assure us that they use the data in a discrete manner. They may not distribute the collected data further and are required to comply with our Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions.

Your data will never be sold to third parties.

**Cookies  
**We may place cookies and or other tracking devices in the user’s browser files. Cookies are used to track user behavior. Based on the collected data, we can improve our products and services.

Cookies can be rejected. If this occurs, portions of the IOS Press Corporate Website may not be properly usable.

**Secure Use of the IOS Press Corporate Website  
**In cooperation with Solcon, our hosting partner, and Limoen, webmaster of this website, we will do everything in our power to guard your personal details and usage behavior data. Collected data will be stored on secure servers and if you make a transaction on our site, you will be in a safe, encrypted area so no one can take advantage of the details you have entered.

**Links to Other Websites  
**Through this website you may be redirected or find links to other websites which are not under the control of IOS Press. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites, nor are we responsible for their Privacy Policy. We encourage you to be aware of the privacy policies of other parties to which we link in case they collect any personal data from you.

**Emails  
**We may occasionally send emails to our users to inform them of important changes to the IOS Press Corporate Website. If you do not want to receive email from us, you can let us know at [market@iospress.nl](mailto:market@iospress.nl). Please write ‘Unsubscribe Corporate Website’ in the subject area.

**Advertisements  
**Third-party advertising may appear on our website. Usage metrics may be shared with the advertisers, but personal data will never be disclosed.

**Changes  
**IOS Press reserves the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time as we see fit. If this occurs, we will update this page and distribute an announcement to users that have opted in to receive news from us to notify them of the changes.

**IOS Press**  
Nieuwe Hemweg 6B  
1013BG Amsterdam  
Tel.: +31 20 688 33 55  
Email: [info@iospress.nl](mailto:info@iospress.nl)

Version: May 2018
